<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<codeBook xsi:schemaLocation="ddi:codebook:2_5 http://www.ddialliance.org/Specification/DDI-Codebook/2.5/XMLSchema/codebook.xsd" version="2.5" xmlns="ddi:codebook:2_5" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<docDscr>
		<citation>
			<titlStmt>
				<titl>DDI2.5 XML CODEBOOK</titl>
			</titlStmt>
		</citation>
	</docDscr>
	<stdyDscr>
		<citation>
			<titlStmt>
				<titl>Dwelling Age Group Counts - 1900-2015 - Local Enterprise Partnerships Geodata Pack: London (E37000023)
				</titl>
				<altTitl/>
			</titlStmt>
			<rspStmt>
				<AuthEnty></AuthEnty>
				<othId/>
			</rspStmt>
			<prodStmt>
				<producer>ESRC Consumer Data Research Centre </producer>
				<copyright>The following attribution statements must be used to acknowledge copyright and source in use of these datasets:
Data provided by the ESRC Consumer Data Research Centre
Dwelling Age Group Counts Geodata Pack by the ESRC Consumer Data Research Centre;
Contains National Statistics data Crown copyright and database right;
Office for National Statistics and Valuation Office Agency. Contains public sector information licensed under the Open Government Licence v3.0.</copyright>
				<fundAg>Economic and Social Research Council</fundAg>
				<grantNo></grantNo>
			</prodStmt>
			<distStmt>
				<depositr></depositr>
				<distDate></distDate>
			</distStmt>
			<serStmt>
				<serName>Dwelling Age Group Counts</serName>
			</serStmt>
			<verStmt>
				<version></version>
			</verStmt>
		</citation>
		<stdyInfo>
			<subject>
				<keyword>E37000023</keyword>
				<keyword>London</keyword>
				<keyword>1900-2015</keyword>
				<topcClas></topcClas>
			</subject>
			<abstract>This geodata pack provides the Dwelling Age Group Counts grouped into approximate 10-year age bands from pre-1900 to 2015  covering the Local Enterprise Partnerships: London (E37000023).
Residential dwelling ages, grouped into approximately 10-year age bands from pre-1900 to 2015. Counts of the numbers of properties in each LSOA (around 1000 properties), in each group. The original source also splits out by council tax bands.
The data is generally rounded (at source) to the nearest 10. However, where there are more than 0 but less than 5 properties, then the value '1' is assigned. Because of the rounding, then the total population may not be equal to the sum of the constitent populations, for some areas.
The 'Mode 1' columns relate to the modal age grouping, i.e. the grouping with the most number of properties in it. 'Mode 2' is the runner-up age grouping, i.e. the grouping with the second-most number of properties in it. It may be that there are two or more groupings with the same maximum population, in which case Mode 1 is assigned to the most recent one, Mode 2 to the second-most recent etc.
			</abstract>
			<sumDscr>
				<timePrd>1900-2015</timePrd>
				<collDate></collDate>
				<nation>England</nation>
				<geogCover>London</geogCover>
				<geogUnit>LSOA</geogUnit>
				<anlyUnit>LSOA</anlyUnit>
				<universe/>
				<dataKind>Shapefile</dataKind>
			</sumDscr>
		</stdyInfo>
		<method>
			<dataColl>
				<timeMeth/>
				<dataCollector>VOA</dataCollector>
				<sampProc/>
				<deviat/>
				<collMode/>
				<sources>
					<dataSrc>Dwelling Age Group Counts 1900-2015</dataSrc>
				</sources>
				<weight/>
			</dataColl>
		</method>
		<dataAccs>
			<setAvail>
				<accsPlac>Consumer Data Research Centre</accsPlac>
				<accsPlac>UK Data Service</accsPlac>
			</setAvail>
			<useStmt>
				<restrctn/>
				<contact>data@cdrc.ac.uk</contact>
			</useStmt>
		</dataAccs>
		<othrStdyMat>
			<relStdy/>
			<relPubl></relPubl>
			<othRefs/>
		</othrStdyMat>
	</stdyDscr>
</codeBook>
